baseballsavings.com 2009-06-27

# Baseball Savings - The Net's Premier Online Baseball Superstore

|    
---  
Privacy Policy   
This Privacy Statement describes the practices pertaining to the collection and handling of personal information from visitors to Baseball Savings. The statement does not pertain to the privacy practices for partnered sites, and we encourage those who visit external sites from links within Baseball Savings to read the privacy policy statements of those sites. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you can contact us via the following: 

  * Online: [Click here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com) to contact Baseball Savings via email (customerservice@baseballsavings.com)
  * Phone: 1- 866-923-5050
  * Mail: Baseball Savings, 8851 E. 34th St. N., Wichita, KS 67226 

In order to make you feel comfortable and secure in our online store, Baseball Savings has taken steps to guard your security while making purchases online. The Privacy Statement describes: 

  * Information Collected
  * Use of Information
  * Information Sharing
  * Aggregate Information
  * Opting Out
  * Sweepstakes Referrals and Tell-A-Friend
  * Information Disclosure Required by Law
  * Cookies
  * Visitor Options
  * Security
  * Children
  * California Privacy Rights
  * Notification of Change

Information Collected  
When you visit Baseball Savings, in order for us to provide you with the products or services that you have requested, you may be asked to provide us with personally identifiable information. For example, when you order a product, you will undergo a checkout process, during which you will be asked for your shipping and billing addresses, a daytime phone number, your e-mail address, and your credit card number or other payment-related information. When purchasing age-restricted products, you will also be asked for your date of birth. If you request one of our newsletters or send an inquiry to one of our customer service representatives, we will also store a record of your request along with your e-mail address. In addition, our Web servers track various technical details about your visit, such as your computer's IP address and which pages you visited, however that information does not typically contain any personally identifiable information about you. 

Back To Top  
  
Use of Information  
The information we collect is used to provide the products and services that you have requested or that we think you might have an interest in. It is also used to improve the content of our Web site, to notify you of problems with your requests, or to update you about changes to our Web site. 

Back To Top  
  
Information Sharing  
In order to operate this Web site and in order to provide you with the products and services you have requested, we occasionally need to share information with third parties. We may transmit your personal information to service providers who assist us in processing orders, shipping products to you, processing your payment information, sending you catalogs, conducting surveys, on and offline sweepstakes, sending you e-mails and newsletters, and helping us decide whether to extend credit to you. We have agreements with these service providers that they will protect your privacy in accordance with our standard Privacy Policy statement. Some of those organizations may have their own Privacy Statements that may give you additional protections, so you are encouraged to read those statements when presented to you. 

We use WebTrends, to help us gather and analyze information about our customers (anonymous traffic, and from time to time, individual user activity) on our website. WebTrends only role is to help us conduct our business and deliver the most relevant products and services. They are not permitted to use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

Back To Top  
  
Aggregate Information  
Baseball Savings may also use data to improve marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve content and product offerings, and to customize site content, layout, and services. Additionally, this data may be shared with third parties on an aggregated basis. 

Back To Top  
  
Opting Out  
Baseball Savings provides site visitors with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving our online communications. If you would like to opt-out of receiving email communications [click here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com). Requests to unsubscribe from email are processed immediately, but you could continue to receive emails, which entered the system prior to processing your request, for up to two days. 

To discontinue the receipt of postal mail, please [click here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com) to email Customer Service asking that your name be removed from our postal mailing list. Please note that you may continue to receive mailings, which entered the system prior to processing your request, for up to 12 weeks. Any mailings that you may receive during this time period do not reflect your subscription status, and we ask you to please disregard them. 

Back To Top  
  
Sweepstakes Referrals and Tell-A-Friend  
If you elect to use the Tell-A-Friend service to inform a friend about a special product on the website or use the Sweepstakes Entry form to enter a referral, you will be asked for an acquaintance's name and email address. Baseball Savings will automatically send this person a one-time e-mail inviting them to either view the product, in the case of Tell-A-Friend, or register to sign-up for the sweepstakes, in the case of the Sweepstakes Entry. These emails may also contain links promoting other areas of our website. 

Back To Top  
  
Information Disclosure Required by Law  
If required by law, we may provide any and all information we have about you to law enforcement or other government agencies, pursuant to a subpoena, warrant, or other order by a court of competent jurisdiction. In all cases, we will require written documentation of the request, proof of the identity of the law enforcement official making the request, and we will take steps to authenticate the validity of the request. Any law enforcement or government agency request submitted with less than a court-issued order will be evaluated on a case-by-case basis according to the need and urgency, as well as the particular law enforcement agency making the request. 

Back To Top  
  
Cookies  
A cookie is a block of text placed in a file on the user's hard drive by a Web site you've visited. These types of cookies cannot identify an individual user specifically, such as by name or address, unless the cookie data is attached to personally identifiable information such as online registration. Baseball Savings uses cookies to observe our site visitor's navigation and track page use. This helps us identify ways to improve the shopping experience. Cookies used for this purpose are not attached to personally identifiable information. 

Baseball Savings also uses cookies to perform functions that must be tied to a specific visitor, such as keeping track of the items in the shopping cart. Cookies serving this purpose are saved for a designated period of time in case the visitor's session expires or they return to complete a purchase within that time frame. 

Back To Top  
  
Visitor Options  
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by email, by calling, or by writing to us at the above postal address and telling us that you do not want to receive email from our company. 

If you provide us with your e-mail address, you may receive messages about your order status, issues regarding the operations of this Web site, and messages from subsidiaries of Baseball Savings and other companies with operational relationships to Baseball Savings. You may modify your e-mail preferences by [clicking here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com) or by calling 1- 866-923-5050. 

If you provide us with your postal address, you may receive periodic catalogs from us, or other notices containing information about new products and services. On occasion, we may make our postal mailing address lists available to subsidiaries and affiliated companies that are part of Baseball Savings family of companies. We may also make our postal mailing address lists available to other direct mail companies who we believe may have products and services of interest to our customers. However, we do not share e-mail addresses with any outside organizations for marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive postal mailings from Baseball Savings, its subsidiaries, or third-party organizations, please let us know by sending an e-mail, calling, or writing to us at the above postal address. Please provide us with your exact name and postal address and state the lists from which you wish to be removed so that we can be sure your information is removed from future mailing lists. 

We will request your telephone number or facsimile (FAX) number, and if you provide it, you may receive telephone or FAX contact from us with information regarding your orders or requests for information. We do not share phone or FAX numbers with third parties for marketing purposes. 

Back To Top  
  
Security  
Baseball Savings values your business and is committed to doing everything possible to make our online ordering process secure. As always, our 100% satisfaction guarantee applies to any and all purchases from Baseball Savings. 

Any credit card information you enter on our site is strongly encrypted by industry-standard protocol, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). Baseball Savings Web site uses SSL to communicate with secure browsers like Netscape and Internet Explorer. These browsers encrypt your credit card and personal information in a way that makes it extremely difficult for anyone to intercept and misuse while being transmitted between your computer and our server. 

Once you have completed your order online, our security procedures do not end. We take appropriate precautions to protect the security and privacy of the information stored on our computer networks. Many of the systems which store your personal information are not connected to the Internet, reducing the likelihood of security breaches. Our systems are also housed in secure facilities, and access to your data by our employees is limited to those in highly specified roles, controlled by password protected systems, and monitored for abuse. 

If you are still unsure of giving your credit card over the Internet, please feel free to phone, fax, or mail your order to us. For telephone ordering or assistance, please call 1- 866-923-5050. Our fax number for orders is 1-888-838-5557. Or, send your order to: Baseball Savings, 8851 E. 34th St. N., Wichita, KS 67226 

If you have any further question regarding your online security, please [click here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com) to e-mail us or contact us by phone at 1- 866-923-5050. 

Back To Top  
  
Children  
In accordance with federal law, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under age 13 without the verifiable permission of a parent or guardian. If you are under age 13, you are welcome to browse our Web site. However you are not permitted to use any of the features of our site that require the collection of any personally identifiable information. If we determine that we have erroneously collected a child's information, we will immediately undertake to delete that data from our records. 

Back To Top  
  
California Privacy Rights  
On January 1, 2005, bill SB27 outlining privacy practices of California businesses and the collection and appropriate use of personal information in direct marketing activities became law. 

Baseball Savings respects and honors all visitor preferences for receiving communications both online and in the mail, as well as for participation in the list rental and exchange program. 

To opt-out of receiving email communications, postal mail or from participating in the list rental and exchange program, or to request a disclosure of list rental and exchange information, please follow the directions below. Any request for personal information will be fulfilled within a reasonable time frame. 

  * Email: [Click here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com) to change your email preferences
  * Postal Mail: [Click here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com) to email Customer Service to change your postal mail preferences
  * Disclosure Request: [Click here](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com) to email Customer Service to request disclosure of list rental and exchange practices

Back To Top  
  
Notification of Change  
Baseball Savings reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Baseball Savings privacy policy will be kept up-to-date and clearly posted on our web site. 

Questions?  E-mail us at: [**customerservice@baseballsavings.com**](mailto:customerservice@baseballsavings.com)

Back To Top
